{"data":[{"question":"________ every child in the school passed the swimming test.","a":"Near to","b":"Near of","c":"Next to","d":"Nearly","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Nearly: almost, but not quite or not completely [= almost].\u00a0\n- Near to; next to= close to.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"She can look back on her career with great ________.","a":"satisfied","b":"satisfaction","c":"satisfactory","d":"satisfactorily","answer":"2","explain":"\n- With + noun\/noun phrase\/Pronoun.\u00a0\n\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"The captain as well as the passengers ________ frightened.","a":"be","b":"been","c":"was","d":"were","answer":"3","explain":"\n- The captain (subject) is singular\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Ann has got two sisters. Both of them ________ married.","a":"has","b":"have","c":"is","d":"are","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Be married.\u00a0\n- Subject (both of them) are plural.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Each learner of English ________ a good dictionary.","a":"needs","b":"need","c":"is","d":"are","answer":"1","explain":"\n- The pronouns each, everyone, every one, everybody, anyone, anybody, someone, and somebody are singular and require singular verbs.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Money, nor fame, nor wealth ________ brought happiness to everybody.","a":"has","b":"have","c":"is","d":"are","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Two singular subjects connected by either\/or or neither\/nor require a singular verb.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"They ________ at this school before they became interpreters.","a":"have taught","b":"had taught","c":"taught","d":"were taught","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Past perfect tense: expresses the idea that something occurred before another action in the past (before they became interpreters).","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"The salary of a bus driver is much higher ________.","a":"in comparison with the salary of a teacher","b":"than a teacher","c":"than that of a teacher","d":"to compare as a teacher","answer":"3","explain":"\n - Thing to compare must be equal- person-person; object-object... \n- That= the salary.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Professional people expect you to call them when it is necessary ________ an appointment.","a":"to cancel","b":"cancel","c":"canceling","d":"canceled","answer":"1","explain":"\n- It's necessary to do sth.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"A computer is usually chosen because of its simplicity of operation and ease of maintenance ________ its capacity to store information.","a":"the same as","b":"the same","c":"as well as","d":"as well","answer":"3","explain":"\n- As well as something\/somebody: in addition to something or someone else.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"}]}